remotepc.com 2019-04-01

# RemotePC™ - Privacy Policy

####  Privacy Policy 

Last Updated: May 08, 2018 

IDrive Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

Users can access IDrive Inc. services (the “Services”) through our websites, applications on Devices, through APIs and through third parties. A “Device” is any computer used to access the Services, including without limitation a desktop computer, laptop, mobile phone, tablet or other consumer electronic device. This Privacy Policy governs your access to IDrive Inc. Services, regardless of how you access it, and by using our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy. All of the different forms of data, content, and information described below are collectively referred to as “information”.

What Information Do We Gather? 

__User Provided Information__ – Due to the nature of our Services, we must collect personal information from users during the registration process including first and last names, a valid credit card to process payment for service, home and/or business postal addresses, an email address and a password. In addition to required member information, we may conduct surveys and ask users to volunteer demographic information to be used on an aggregate basis for internal market research and/or joint research projects with outside companies involved in product development. You may also ask us to import your contacts by giving us access to your Device(s), third party services (for example, your email account) or to use your social networking information if you give us access to your account on social network connection services. You may also provide us with your contacts’ email addresses when sharing folders or files with them.

__Session Records__ \- To maintain our quality of service and to assist in the analysis of product performance, we may also gather data on connection information, including the timing and size of all packets sent over the Internet during a session, session date and times, Device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, Device name and/or identification number, and other interactions with the Service. The gathered information is used to ensure the highest quality experience possible. 

__Cookies__ \- We use “cookies” to collect information and improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your Device. We may use “persistent cookies” to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Service. We may use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Service. The cookies are used solely for identifying user sessions and do not store any personal information regarding the user. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of the Service. 

What Do We Do With Gathered Information? 

Information gathered by us may be used: (i) to provide and improve our Service, (ii) to administer your use of the Service, (iii) to better understand your needs and interests, (iv) to personalize and improve your experience, (v) to provide or offer software updates and (vi) to provide product announcements. For example, email addresses provided by you may be used to send periodic information about our Services and related products. In order to present the best possible product to the public, we track the category of services selected by our individual users as well as all information pertaining to user satisfaction. We reserve the right to maintain evaluation and feedback records indefinitely. 

Our website provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. If you wish to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service you can go to your personal profile (after logging into our Service) and uncheck the option to receive communications regarding our services or use the unsubscribe link within email communications. 

Who Do We Share Information With?

We do not voluntarily share personally identifiable information with any third party without the user's express consent or unless compelled by applicable state and federal laws (see below). We do not control the practices of our affiliates. If you have questions about how affiliates use the information gathered when you link to them, please read their privacy policies. Our site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

__Users__ – We will display your personal information in your profile page. You can review and revise your profile information at any time by accessing your account settings. We may also share or disclose your information with your consent, for example if you use a third party application to access your account (see below). 

__Service Providers, Business Partners and Others__ \- We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyze, and improve the Service (including but not limited to database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Service’s features). These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy. 

__Third-Party Applications__ \- We may share your information with a third party application with your consent, for example when you choose to access our Services through a third-party application. We are not responsible for what those parties do with your information, so you should make sure you trust the application and that it has a privacy policy acceptable to you. 

__Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of IDrive Inc.’s Rights__ \- We may disclose to parties outside IDrive Inc. information about you that we collect when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (ii) protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury; (iii) prevent fraud or abuse of our Services or its users; or (iv) to protect our property rights. 

__Business Transfers__ \- If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction, but we will notify you (for example, via email and/or a prominent notice on our website) of any change in control or use of your personal information or files, or if either become subject to a different Privacy Policy. We will also notify you of choices you may have regarding the information. 

__Non-private or Non-Personal Information__ \- We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage statistics of our Service. Our Service may also offer publicly accessible community services such as blogs, forums, and wikis. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. Your posts may remain even after you cancel your account. 

Changing Your Information

After successfully logging in to the Service from our website, you can correct, amend or delete information related to your account as well as opt-in or out of receiving communications regarding our Service. 

Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you our Services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you Services, you may delete your account through the account settings after logging in to our Service from our website. Your files will automatically be removed from our servers within 10 business days of cancellation. Please note, that there might be latency in deleting backed-up versions of files that may exist after deletion. We may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

Security

We take reasonable precautions to protect personal information in our possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. User data is password protected and your password should never be shared with anyone. When we receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information we redirect visitors to the secure portion of our site using industry standard SSL. 

Our Policy Towards Children

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@remotepc.com](mailto:privacy@remotepc.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to delete such information from our files. 

EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield

IDrive Inc. has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. and Swiss–U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union member countries and Switzerland to the United States. IDrive complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal information from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions. You can find IDrive’s Privacy Shield certification [here](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list). You can also learn more about Privacy Shield at [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

IDrive is subject to oversight by the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. JAMS is the US-based independent organization responsible for reviewing and resolving complaints about our Privacy Shield compliance. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact JAMS at <https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield> (free of charge). In the event your concern still isn't addressed by JAMS, you may be entitled to binding [arbitration](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint) under Privacy Shield and its principles. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we make a change to this privacy policy that we believe materially reduces your rights, we will provide you with notice (for example, by email). We may provide notice of changes in other circumstances as well. By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this website you can contact: 

**Attn: Privacy Management**  
IDrive Inc.   
26115 Mureau Road, Suite A,  
Calabasas, CA 91302.
